{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Lawn Fertilizing Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","__cache./api/resource/task/40319/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40319,"taskName":"Lawn Care - Fertilize or Treat a Lawn","taskDescription":"Fertilize, Feed or Treat a Lawn","xmTaskDescriptor":"Lawn Fertilizing Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":356,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Feed fertilization frontyard organic supply","textMessagingName":"Chem Lawn Care","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes chemical lawn treatments as well a natural approaches to a healthier lawn.","rolloverShortDesc":"Fertilizer, weed killer, pesticides, natural remedies.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Fertilize, Feed or Treat a Lawn.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Lawn Fertilization \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Lawn \u0026 Garden Fertilization \u0026 Treatment","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":48,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Fertilize or Treat a Lawn","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Lawn Care - Fertilize or Treat a Lawn","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Lawn Care Project","urlName":"Lawn-Care-Fertilize-or-Treat-a-Lawn","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Lawn Fertilization Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Feed,fertilization,organic,supply,yard,landscape,landsacaping,seed,grass,geo-landscaping,gardeners,garden,fertilizer,backyard,chemical,Fertilize,Care,Lawn,hydroseeding, lawncare","emcCategoryOid":-12047,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":617,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40319/":{"taskOID":40319,"originalTaskOID":40319,"setID":617,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6209,"questionDisplayText":"Lawn Care Services Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What lawn care services are needed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Weed control","answerDisplayText":"Weed control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8189,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lawn analysis","answerDisplayText":"Lawn analysis","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Natural fertilizers","answerDisplayText":"Natural fertilizers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8192,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Seeding","answerDisplayText":"Seeding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8193,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8195,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Mineral application","answerDisplayText":"Mineral application","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8196,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Core aeration/plugging","answerDisplayText":"Core aeration/plugging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6210,"questionDisplayText":"Lawn area in square feet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate size of your lawn area?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8198,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2,500 (Small)","answerDisplayText":"Small: less than 2,500","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8199,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2,500 - 5,000 (Medium)","answerDisplayText":"Medium: 2,500 - 5,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8200,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5,000 - 10,000 (Large)","answerDisplayText":"Large 5,000 - 10,000 (1/4 Acre)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8201,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","answerDisplayText":"Very large: 10,000 - 20,000 (1/2 Acre)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8202,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","answerDisplayText":"Huge: more than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6209,"questionDisplayText":"Lawn Care Services Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What lawn care services are needed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Weed control","answerDisplayText":"Weed control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8189,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lawn analysis","answerDisplayText":"Lawn analysis","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Natural fertilizers","answerDisplayText":"Natural fertilizers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8192,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Seeding","answerDisplayText":"Seeding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8193,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8195,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Mineral application","answerDisplayText":"Mineral application","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8196,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Core aeration/plugging","answerDisplayText":"Core aeration/plugging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8188,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Weed control","answerDisplayText":"Weed control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8189,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Insect control","answerDisplayText":"Insect control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8190,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lawn analysis","answerDisplayText":"Lawn analysis","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Natural fertilizers","answerDisplayText":"Natural fertilizers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8192,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Seeding","answerDisplayText":"Seeding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8193,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Disease control","answerDisplayText":"Disease control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8195,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Mineral application","answerDisplayText":"Mineral application","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8196,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Core aeration/plugging","answerDisplayText":"Core aeration/plugging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6210,"questionDisplayText":"Lawn area in square feet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate size of your lawn area?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8198,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2,500 (Small)","answerDisplayText":"Small: less than 2,500","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8199,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2,500 - 5,000 (Medium)","answerDisplayText":"Medium: 2,500 - 5,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8200,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5,000 - 10,000 (Large)","answerDisplayText":"Large 5,000 - 10,000 (1/4 Acre)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8201,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","answerDisplayText":"Very large: 10,000 - 20,000 (1/2 Acre)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8202,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","answerDisplayText":"Huge: more than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8198,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 2,500 (Small)","answerDisplayText":"Small: less than 2,500","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8199,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2,500 - 5,000 (Medium)","answerDisplayText":"Medium: 2,500 - 5,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8200,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5,000 - 10,000 (Large)","answerDisplayText":"Large 5,000 - 10,000 (1/4 Acre)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8201,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"10,000 - 20,000 (Very large)","answerDisplayText":"Very large: 10,000 - 20,000 (1/2 Acre)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8202,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","answerDisplayText":"Huge: more than 20,000 (1/2 Acre +)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}